seagate.com 2002-04-08

# Seagate Technology Privacy Statement

**Seagate respects your right to privacy**  
As a leading provider of storage solutions, Seagate knows the value of information. We also understand the inherent privacy risks involved in using the Internet. This statement describes privacy practices that apply to the entire Seagate family of external Web sites. Please note that these sites may contain links to third-party Web sites over which Seagate maintains no control and therefore takes no responsibility regarding privacy considerations or content. Generally, you may browse Seagate's Web sites anonymously. However, on some occasions we may ask you to provide identifying information. Wherever possible, we try to provide you with opportunities to review and change any personal information that is collected. Seagate may update this privacy statement from time to time. You are encouraged to review this statement regularly for any changes.

**Why we collect information online**  
Seagate collects information online to enhance your use of our Web sites, to determine what products and services you desire, to provide you requested customer services, to allow you convenient access to our current products and services and to make our future products and services available to you.

**Summary of information that Seagate gathers online**  
Seagate collects three types of information from visitors to our Web sites: (1) information gathered by analyzing page views and user navigation patterns, (2) information that you provide directly when you use various Seagate services or participate in various Seagate programs, and (3) information that you provide prior to purchasing Seagate products online.

**How Seagate uses the information gathered online**  
Because Seagate is a worldwide company some of your information may be shared with internal Seagate business units and affiliated companies around the world to help Seagate create and deliver products and services for our customers.

Seagate uses tracking information to identify the areas of our Web sites that are most heavily utilized. We do this to improve the usefulness and effectiveness of our Web sites by creating and delivering content that is most useful to you. The information that you provide while visiting Seagate's Web sites will be used to improve the sites themselves, to provide interactive or personalized elements on the site, and to prepare future content based on your interests.

Seagate uses information that you voluntarily provide to allow you to participate in online programs, services (including online ordering, order tracking and technical support) and promotions. Sometimes we will use third parties to administer our programs, services or promotions. In such instances we may share your information with those third parties solely for the purpose of performing their administrative functions.

Seagate may use information that you voluntarily provide to send you electronic newsletters and information regarding products, programs and promotions. We use demographic information you provide to target our newsletters and information to the appropriate audience. Seagate may also share your information with other reputable technology companies whose products or services we think you may find interesting. If you do not wish to receive these newsletters or have your information shared with other companies simply email your request to the Seagate webmaster ([webmaster@seagate.com](mailto:webmaster@seagate.com)). Members of the Seagate Reseller Partner Program for Storage Solutions can alter their profile and unsubscribe by emailing the program specialist at [reseller_partner@seagate.com](mailto:reseller_partner@seagate.com).

Seagate uses email as an avenue with which to provide customer service and technical support. We may use information that you voluntarily provide us to contact you in an attempt to resolve a prior issue or to proactively notify you of technical issues which may affect you. We may also use this information to invite you to participate in a voluntary survey to help us improve our programs and services.

**Site Security**  
Seagate's Web sites use a variety of security measures to prevent the loss, misuse, or alteration of information you send to Seagate. The measures taken to protect your information include the use of secure software encryption (SSL). The personal information you provide, such as credit card data, name and address, are encrypted prior to transmission to Seagate.

**A few notes about Cookies**  
Like many Web sites, Seagate's sites may make use of "cookies". A cookie is a short line of text that is created by a Web site and stored in a file on your computer. Cookies are used to store information about your preferences and activity during and after your visit to a Web site. Cookies are also used widely in electronic commerce programs to keep track of which items a user has selected for purchase. Cookies cannot gather any information from your computer other than that which you provide directly or that which is provided routinely by your browser software.

**Note:** Most browsers can be set to tell when a cookie is sent - at which time you can refuse to receive it. If you have set your browser to not accept cookies you may not be able to use or take full advantage of some Seagate Web sites.

If you have any questions or feedback concerning Seagate's privacy policy please contact [webmaster@seagate.com](mailto:webmaster@seagate.com).

TOP
